revou.com 2012-06-11

# Twitter clone PHP social networking script. Micro blogging social network software - IM/SMS/Web. Start your own site just like twitter and jaiku.

Privacy Statement for REVOU  
REVOU has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: ReVou.com

Personal Information  
Any information we collect, including your e-mail and mailing address, are not shared with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes except where explicitly implied.

External Links  
This site contains links to other sites. REVOU is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Public Sections and FAQ  
This site makes product infromation and FAQ available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal or server information.

Date Security  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. No one can view your account information without your password, which you can change anytime you want.

Site Usage Information

Similar to other commercial web sites, our web site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" and web server logs to collect information about how our web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed and time spent at our web site.

Contacting REVOU  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can us at:

Feb 19, 2010

Aug 20, 2009

Apr 28, 2009

Feb 02, 2009

Jan 23, 2009

Jan 20, 2009

Dec 18, 2008

[ Why is Twitter an indispensable tool not only for you but...](http://blog.revou.com/2008/12/18/why-is-twitter-an-indispensable-tool-not-only-for-you-but-also-for-companies-who-are-reaching-out-to-consumers/)

Sep 29, 2008

Sep 11, 2008

Aug 07, 2008

July 24, 2008

July 1, 2008  

June 25, 2008

June 20, 2008
